Guide to the William F. Wu Comics Collection MSS.244
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series V: Deadly Hands of Kung Fu, 167441
  - The Deadly Hands of Kung Fu (20-24), January 1976- May 1976; 213865 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - The Deadly Hands of Kung Fu (25- 29), June 1976- October 1976; 213866 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - The Deadly Hands of Kung Fu (30-33), November 1976- February 1977; 213867 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - The Deadliest Hereos of Kung Fu (1), Summer 1975; 213868 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Series VI: Charlton Comics, 212163
  - Subseries A: Doomsday +1, 212199
    - Doomsday +1 (2-6), September 1975- May 1976; 213870 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Subseries B: House of Yang, 212200
    - Yang (1,2,4), November 1973- Spetember 1974; 213871 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Yang (5-9), November 1974- September 1975; 213872 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Yang (11-13), January 1976- May 1976; 213873 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - House of Yang (1-4), July 1975- February 1976; 213874 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Subseries C: Various, 212201
    - Battlefield Action (69), June 1981; 213875 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - The Charlton Bullyseye (3), 1975; 213876 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Fightin' Marines (116), January 1974; 213877 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Ghostly Tales (113), February 1975; 213878 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Haunted (91), October 1966; 213879 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Hong Kong Phooey (2), 1975; 213880 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Six Million Dollar Man (9), June 1976; 213881 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Series VII: Various Comics, 212202
  - Subseries A: Judo Masters, 213869
    - Judo Master (91), October 1966; 213887 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Judo Master (98), 1967; 213888 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Subseries B: Atlas Comics, 213882
    - The Hands of the Dragon (9), June 1975; 213889 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Men's Adventures (17), December 1952; 213890 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - SGT. Stryker's Death Squad (1-3), February- July 1975; 213891 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Subseries C: Dell Comics, 213886
    - Andy Panda (404), 1952; 213927 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - The Conquerer (690), 1956; 213928 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Mighty Samson (24), June 1974; 213929 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - The Sword and the Dragon (118), 1960; 213930 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Subseries D: Gold Key Comics, 213883
    - Amazing Chan and the Chan Clan (4), 1973; 213892 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Island at the Top of the World (27), February 1975; 213893 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - M.A.R.S. Patrol (8), February 1969; 213894 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Mighty Mouse (109), December 1966; 213895 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Star Trek (26), September 1974; 213896 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Subseries E: Various Comics, 213884
    - The Art of Neal Adams, 1975; 213897 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - The Badger (14), August 1986; 213898 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - The Best Warriors of Shaolin (1), July 1987; 213899 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Betty and Me (1), 1967; 213900 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Captain Steve Savage and the Rockets of Death (5), 1952; 213901 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Capt. Storm, October 1966; 213902 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Challengers of the Unknown (61), April- May 1968; 213903 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Charlie Chan (1,2,2), 1958-1966; 213904 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Charlie Chan (1,2), 1989; 213905 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - E-Man (22,23), February- April 1985; 213906 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Fight Comics (48, 56, 81), 1947- 1952; 213907 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Flash Gordon in the Mystic Realm (16), 1969; 213908 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Green Hornet (19), 1944; 213909 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - The Hard Way (53), Undated; 213910 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Jumbo Comics (87, 101, 105, 109), 1946- 1948; 213911 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Magnus Robot Fighter 4000 A.D. (15), 1966; 213912 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Ninja Funnies (1), 1987; 213913 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Orb (4,5), 1975- 1976; 213914 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Fantagraphic Books Presents Will Gould's Red Barry, 1989; 213915 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Red Dragon (1), November 1947; 213916 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Rotten Comics Fantastic Adventure Stories (1), January 1975; 213917 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - SGT. Rock (260, 265), November 1973- February 1974; 213918 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Thrilling Adventure Stories (2), August 1975; 213919 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Thunder Agents (18), September 1968; 213920 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Tod Holton Super Green Beret (1,2), 1967; 213921 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Tzu the Reaper (Preview), 1997; 213922 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Uncle Scrooge (106), 1973; 213923 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - The Unknown Soldier (173, 209, 221), 1973, 1977, 1978; 213924 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - X- Men (64), January 1970; 213925 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Zip Comics (44), 1944; 213926 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Subseries F: Foreign Comics, 213885
    - Superman (Hong Kong), 1972; 213931 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - World Fairy Tales Series: Legends of Chinca nd Mga Alamat ng Tsina, 1973; 213932 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - Lian Huan Hua Bao (4), 1975; 213971 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Dragon Tiger Gate (106, 211), Undated; 213972 (Box 6, Folder 48)
      General note
      Series Title: Dragon Tiger Gate (Long Hu Men) Issue 106: "Subduing Dragon vs. Copper Lion" (Xiang Long Dou Tong) Author: Tony Wong (Huang Yulang)
      Series Title: Dragon Tiger Gate (Long Hu Men) Issue 211: "The Misfortune of Ma Xiaoling" or "Ma Xiaoling's Misfortune" (Xiaoling Luo Nan) Author: Tony Wong (Huang Yulang)
    - Bruce Lee (62, 63), Undated; 213984 (Box 6, Folder 49)
      Series Title: Bruce Lee (Li Xiaolong) Issue 62: "Yin Yang Double Fiends" (Yin Yang Shuang Sha) Author: Shangguan Xiaobao
      Series Title: Bruce Lee (Li Xiaolong) Issue 63: "Running Amok in the Red Light District" (Da Nao Hong Deng Qu) Author: Shangguan Xiaobao
- OVERSIZE Series II, 214797
  - What If? (Splash Page) (9)/ Master of Kung Fu splash Page (19,29,30), 1974- 1975; 1978; 214798 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Master of Kung Fu (Splash Page) (31,34), 1975; 214799 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Master of Kung Fu (Splash Page) (46, 50, 71, 73), 1976-1979; 214800 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Master of Kung Fu (Splash Page) (76,84), 1979; 214801 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Master of Kung Fu (Splash Page) (87,97), 1980; 214802 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Series VIII: 2018 Accretion
  Scope and Contents
  This accretion to the William F. Wu Comics Collection contains comic books, pulp magazines, and books dating from 1920 to 2001. These publications consist of racist and xenophobic Asian stereotypes and include the comic Master of Kung Fu and reproductions of 1930s pulp magazines.
  Arrangement
  This series has not been arranged by an archivist. The materials are arranged in the order in which they were received from the donor.
  - Master of Kung Fu, 1974-1982 (Box 8, Folder 1-21, Box 9, Folder 1-2)
  - Batman and The Atom, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Yellow Claw, Undated (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Books, 1920-2001 (Box 9, Folder 15-18, Box 10, Folder 1-6)
  - Pulp magazines, 1934 (Box 10, Folder 7-15)
  - Scrapbook, 1973 (Box 11)